blinklist.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Blinklist.com

**BlinkList** takes individual privacy very seriously. We are also aware of the threats to your security and privacy on the Internet. Please take a few moments to review the steps that BlinkList takes to ensure your privacy and security while giving you the best possible customer service as you use our web sites.

We may collect personal information, including email addresses, when individuals register to use the BlinkList website and services, post a link to the BlinkList website or submit questions, comments or bug reports. We may also, at times, collect our users’ IP addresses and information regarding our users’ use of our website and services. We may use such IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement within our website and, if necessary, deny service in accordance with our Terms of Service. We may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times, browser type and other technical or performance based statistics.

When you sign-up with BlinkList, we will add your e-mail address into a database. We do not give email addresses to outside companies. We will also never rent or sell out any email addresses.

When you register with BlinkList, you will automatically receive a welcome message, and tips and tricks on how to get the most out of BlinkList and other services that may be of interest to you. At any time, you can opt out of these communications from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link contained in the emails.

In order to offer and provide optimized and personalized services, we use cookies to store and sometimes track information about our users. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user’s browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user’s computer hard drive. Please also note:

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this website.
  * Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on a visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Blinklist may also from time to another serve advertisement from other vendors, for example [Yahoo! & Media.net](http://contextualads.yahoo.net/).
  * Anyone may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads preference manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/) and/or for other vendors at [AboutAds.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

Visit your BlinkList Options page to edit your profile and other information. When you’re signed in, BlinkList page headers will include a link to Settings. You can delete all of your links and personal information from the BlinkList Options page.

BlinkList reserves the right to modify all or some of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. We will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization from the appropriate user(s) to do otherwise.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website or your dealings with this BlinkList, you can send an e-mail, in English, to [feedback@blinklist.com](mailto:feedback@blinklist.com).

Read our [Terms of Service](http://blinklist.com/static/terms-of-service)
